http://www.catherines.com/help/privacy-policy#california

Skip to main content
Accessibility Policy
https://www.catherines.com
/on/demandware.static/Sites-oss-Site/-/default/dwba6c5881/images/ca/primarylogo.png
Effective Date: January 1, 2020
The FULLBEAUTY Brands family of brands, which includes Woman Within®, Jessica London®, Roaman's®, SwimsuitsForAll®, FullBeauty®, Ellos®, KingSize®, BrylaneHome® and any other brands owned or operated by FULLBEAUTY Brands, Inc. or any of its affiliates from time to time (collectively, “FULLBEAUTY Brands”), understands that you care about how we collect, use, and share information when you interact with our websites, social media sites and handles, email and online services (our “Services”) and we value the trust you place in us. This Privacy Policy explains:
the types of information we collect through our Services
how we use and protect that information
the types of information we may share with others and under what circumstances
the choices you have regarding our collection, use and sharing practices
details regarding our use of third party cookies and other tracking technologies
We also include specific disclosures for residents of California.
This Policy applies to all of the FULLBEAUTY Brands websites (collectively, the “FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites”), as well as social media sites and handles, your email address, emails we send, as well as the information we collect when you interact with us through other online services. It also applies anywhere it is linked. It does not apply to non-FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites and mobile applications that may link to the Services or be linked to or from the Services; please review the privacy policies on those websites and applications directly to understand their privacy practices.
For questions about our privacy practices, contact us at:
FULLBEAUTY Brands, Inc.
One New York Plaza
New York, NY 10004
Attn: General Counsel
Email: PrivacyOfficer@fbbrands.com
Information We Collect
Information you give us: Some of the Services may include features or services that permit you to enter contact information and other information about you. We collect and store any information you enter on our Services. This includes:
Contact and demographic information when registering to use our Services.
Payment information and associated contact information when engaging in a transaction on any FULLBEAUTY Brands Website. For international shipments, we may be required to collect special import identification numbers for customs purposes.
Email address information when subscribing to our emails.
Any information or data you provide by interacting in our chat, by submitting a product review, or by commenting on content posted on our Services.
Information you provide when you complete a survey administered by us or a service provider acting on our behalf.
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence and any contact information provided. We record telephone conversations with our customer service center for record-keeping, training, and quality assurance purposes.
Information We Collect From Others: We may receive information about you from external parties in order to allow us to provide joint service offerings or inform you about products that we think you may be interested in. This includes:
Contact information and information about your transaction if you purchase one of our products from a third-party seller.
Information about you, including mailing address or email address and other information about your potential interests and demographics, in order to send you catalogs, product offerings, or promotional offers. We may also send you branded private label credit card offers based on demographic information we receive.
Contact information from someone you know who purchased a product for you or provided your information through a referral program.
Information We Collect Automatically: When you interact with the Services, certain information about your use of our Services is automatically collected. Much of this information is collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies, as well as through your web browser or device.
This includes:
Details of your visits to any of our FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites and information generated in the course of the use our site (including the timing, frequency and pattern of service use) including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, the resources that you access, and how you reached our site.
Details regarding the device you use to access our Services, including, but not limited to, your IP address, operating system and browser type.
Information about how you interact with our ads and newsletters, including whether you open or click links in any correspondence.
Information that you make available to us on a social media platform (such as by clicking on a social media icon linked from our Services), including your account ID or username and other information included in your posts.
How We Use and Protect Your Information
We may use the information we collect from you for the following purposes:
To provide you with our products and services, including to take steps to transact a sale or for services, process payments, fulfill orders, and send service communications.
To enable additional features on our Services and to provide you with a personalized service.
To notify you regarding products, services, and promotions that may be if interest to you.
To create custom audiences on social media sites.
To provide you with the best service and improve and grow our business, including understanding our customer base and purchasing trends, and understanding the effectiveness of our marketing, and tailoring advertising to you.
To detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be fraudulent or illegal, and to comply with legal requirements regarding the provision of products and services.
How We Secure the Information We Collect From or About You
We use a combination of physical, technical, and administrative safeguards to protect the information we collect through the Services.
While we use these precautions to safeguard your information, we cannot guarantee the security of the networks, systems, servers, devices, and databases we operate or that are operated on our behalf.
Our Sharing of Your Information
Service Providers: We engage vendors to perform functions on our behalf such as: website, software, and data storage, content management, customer communications, database management, technical integration, marketing automation, analytics, website optimization, conducting customer surveys, shipping, and payment processing.There are limited circumstances in which the service provider collects data directly from you when their privacy policies may also apply.
Social Media Platforms: Where you choose to interact with us through social media, your interaction with these programs typically allows the third party to collect some information about you through digital cookies they place on your device and other tracking mechanisms. In some cases, the third party may recognize you through its digital cookies even when you do not interact with their application. Please visit the third parties’ respective privacy policies to better understand their data collection practices and controls they make available to you.
Branded Private Label Credit Card Accounts: If you hold a branded private label credit card, we share information with the bank that issues branded private label credit card accounts, Comenity Bank. Shared information includes the date of the order, the type of payment, the amount of the order, and similar items, and may also include your name, address or other contact information. To obtain a privacy policy, opt-out information, or contact information, for any of the branded private label credit card programs, you may contact the Bank by clicking through to the following link: https://comenity.com/.
Third parties involved in advertising: We partner with third parties who assist us in serving advertising regarding the Services to others who may be interested in the Services. We also partner with third parties who use cookies to display interest-based advertising to you on the Services. These third parties may use tracking technologies on our FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites to collect or receive information from the Services and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. These third parties may allow other companies to access information about you so that they may market other products you may be interested in.
Many digital advertising companies post their privacy practices online and may offer you options to control your information.
Corporate Affiliates: Our FULLBEAUTY Brands family shares data with members of our group of companies and brands.
Similar Companies:
We may share your mailing address directly with other companies who may sell services of interest to you. These companies are limited to using the address once for a mailing.
Additional Information About our Data Collection and Sharing Practices
Information Relating to Children: We believe it is important to safeguard the privacy of children and encourage parents to regularly monitor their children’s use of online activities. You must be age 18 or older to use this website or any of our services.
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18 years old.
If you are a parent and believe that your child under the age of 18 has accessed and/or used our website or services or otherwise provided personal information to us, please contact us at or the mailing address at the end of this Privacy Policy and we will work to delete that account and any such personal information.
Legal Disclosures: If we are required to disclose customer information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, in response to law enforcement inquiry or in compliance with applicable laws, we will make such disclosure. We also may share information with legal authorities and other companies for purposes of fraud protection.
Sharing of Aggregated Data: We may analyze aggregated, de-identified data and share these analyses at our discretion, including with marketing agencies, media agencies and analytics providers. These third parties will not be able to relate this data to identifiable individuals.
Combination of Information: We may combine information from the Services together and with other information we obtain from our business records. Additionally, information collected about you from a particular browser or device may be linked to information collected from another computer or device that we believe relates to you.
Personal Data Collected From You About Others: If you decide to refer a friend to us, we will collect your and the third party’s names, e-mail addresses, street addresses, and/or phone numbers in order to send an e-mail or catalog and use this information to communicate with both you and your friend. You hereby agree that you will obtain the third party’s consent to this before giving us their personal data. You hereby agree not to send us the contact details of any legal minor. We will inform any friend you invite that he/she was referred by you in the invitation e-mail.
Change of Ownership or Corporate Organization:
We may transfer to another entity or its affiliates or service providers some or all information about you in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, acquisition, sale of assets or any line of business, change in ownership control, or financing transaction. We cannot promise that an acquiring party or the merged entity will have the same privacy practices or treat your information the same as described in this Policy.
Cross-border Transfer of Data: If you use our Services outside of the United States, you understand that we may collect, process, and store your personal information in the United States and other countries.
The laws in the U.S. regarding personal information may be different from the laws of your state or country.
Any such transfers will comply with safeguards as required by relevant law.
By using the Services, you consent to the collection, international transfer, storage, and processing of your data.
Your Options and Rights
Please visit the My Account page to update your contact information and payment method.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email bulletin or email us at Unsubscribe@fbbrands.com and we will promptly remove you from all correspondence.
If you would like to be removed from a paper catalog mailing list, you can email us by going to the relevant FULLBEAUTY Brands Website listed on the table below and clicking on the email link in the "Contact Us" section. Please make sure to provide us with your exact name and address as it appears on the mailing label from your catalog so that we can identify you correctly.
Woman Within
Phone:
1-800-248-2000
Address:
500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912
Website:
https://www.womanwithin.com/
Brylane Home
Phone:
1-800-528-5150
Address:
500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912
Website:
https://www.brylanehome.com/
Ellos
Phone:
1-800-405-3650
Address:
500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912
Website:
https://www.ellos.us/
Roaman's
Phone:
1-800-436-0800
Address:
500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912
Website:
https://www.roamans.com/
King Size
Phone:
1-800-846-1600
Address:
500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912
Website:
https://www.kingsize.com/
Jessica London
Phone:
1-800-784-1667
Address:
500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912
Website:
https://www.jessicalondon.com/
FullBeauty
Phone:
1-800-400-4481
Address:
500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912
Website:
https://www.fullbeauty.com/
We will make every effort to implement any choice you make as soon as possible, but you should allow up to three months for mailing change requests to be fully implemented. Any mailings that you may receive during this time do not reflect your subscription status, and we ask that you please disregard them.
Special Information for California Residents
Persons with disabilities may obtain this notice in alternative format upon request by contacting us at PrivacyOfficer@fbbrands.com or calling 1-800-781-9168
California Shine the Light: Residents of the State of California have the right to request information from FULLBEAUTY Brands regarding other companies to whom the company has disclosed certain categories of information during the preceding year for those companies’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please email PrivacyOfficer@fbbrands.com or write to us at FULLBEAUTY Brands, Inc., One New York Plaza, New York, NY 10004, Attn: General Counsel.
California Consumer Privacy Act:
The California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) provides California residents with rights to receive certain disclosures regarding the collection, use, and sharing of “Personal Information,” as well as rights to know/access, delete, and limit sharing of Personal Information. The CCPA defines “Personal Information” as “information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household.” Certain information we collect may be exempt from the CCPA because it is considered public information (i.e., it is made available by a government entity) or covered by a specific federal privacy law, such as the Gramm–Leach–Bliley Act, the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act, or the Fair Credit Reporting Act.
To the extent that we collect Personal Information that is subject to the CCPA, that information, our practices, and your rights are described below.
Right to Notice at Collection Regarding the Categories of Personal Information Collected
You have the right to receive notice of the categories of Personal Information we collect, and the purposes for which those categories of Personal Information will be used. The categories we use to describe the information are those enumerated in the CCPA.
Personal Identifiers:
We collect your name, email address, and postal address when you create an account or complete a transaction. If you choose to create an account, we will assign one or more unique identifiers to your profile. We also collect the name and postal address of gift recipients if you use our Services to ship an order directly to them. We use this information to provide the Services, respond to requests, and send information and advertisements.
We collect your social media handle and basic account information when you interact with our Services through social media.
We use this information to improve our Services, respond to your requests or complaints, and to send information and advertisements to you.
We collect unique alphanumeric identifiers, assigned to you by first and third-party cookies, automatically when you use our Services in order to identify you, provide the Services, keep you logged in to the Services, prevent fraud, and provide you with targeted information and offers.
We collect payment information when you provide it to us, which may include your credit card number or a bank account number when you complete a transaction. You may have the option to store this information to your account or set up a recurring transaction. We use this information to streamline and facilitate payments and transactions.
We do not collect your Social Security number, Driver’s License number, and Passport number.
We do not collect medical information and health information about you.
We collect your IP address automatically when you use our Services. We use this information to identify you, gauge online activity on our website, measure the effectiveness of online services, applications, and tools, and serve targeted advertisements based on your online activities.
We collect your device ID automatically when you use our Services. We use this information to monitor your use and the effectiveness of our Services, to identify you, and to provide you with targeted information and offers.
Protected Classifications: We may collect your age in order to verify your identity in connection with specific Services. We may collect your gender, race, ethnic origin, and religion to measure the appeal and effectiveness of our Services with members of particular groups, and to provide you with targeted information, advertisements, and offers.
Commercial Information: When you engage in transactions with us, we create records of goods or services purchased or considered, as well as purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. We use this information to measure the effectiveness of our Services, evaluate products that are of interest to you, follow up on abandoned orders, and provide you with targeted information, advertisements and offers.
Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity Information: We collect information about your browsing history, search history, information regarding your interaction with our websites, and applications or advertisements automatically when you utilize our Services. We use this information to gauge online activity on our website, measure the effectiveness of online services, applications, and tools, and to serve targeted advertisements based on your online activities.
Geolocation Data: As described above, we collect your IP address automatically when you use our Services. We may be able to determine your general location based on the IP address. If you allow your device to provide us with this information, we use it to make improvements to our products and Services, and to provide recommendations and deliver relevant advertising.
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information: If you contact us via phone, we may record the call. We will notify you if a call is being recorded at the beginning of the call. You may have the option to submit images of yourself to us in connection with some of our Services. We do not otherwise collect your photographic or video image, thermal, and olfactory similar information. We use this information to monitor our customer service, maintain the security of our systems and physical locations, and train employees.
Professional or Employment-related Information: We collect information about your professional history. We use this information to improve our Services and to promote our Services to others.
Education Information: We collect information about the level of education you have attained. We use this information to improve our Services and to promote our Services to others.
Inferences drawn to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences or characteristics: We may analyze your actual or likely preferences, as well as actual or inferred demographic information about you, through a series of computer processes. On some occasions, we may add these observations to your internal profile. We use this information to gauge and develop our marketing activities, measure the appeal and effectiveness of our Services, applications, and tools, and to provide you with targeted information, advertisements, and offers.
We may use any of the categories of information listed above for other business or operational purposes compatible with the context in which the Personal Information was collected.
We may share any of the above-listed information with Service Providers, which are companies that we engage for business purposes to conduct activities on our behalf. Service Providers are restricted from using Personal Information for any purpose that is not related to our engagement. The categories of Service Providers with whom we share information and the services they provide are described in our Privacy Policy above in the section titled “Our Sharing of Your Information.”
We also sell some information to third parties, as described below. To opt out of the sale of your information visit our Do Not Sell My Information page. Our full Privacy Policy can be found at each of the FULLBEAUTY Brands websites listed below.
Brand
Website
Woman Within
https://www.womanwithin.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-ww
Brylane Home
https://www.brylanehome.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-bh
Ellos
https://www.ellos.us/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-el
Roaman's
https://www.roamans.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-rm
King Size
https://www.kingsize.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-ks
Jessica London
https://www.jessicalondon.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-jl
Swimsuits For All
https://www.swimsuitsforall.com/help/privacyPolicy.php
FullBeauty
https://www.fullbeauty.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-fb
Right to Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed, or Sold
You have the right to request that we disclose to you the Personal Information we collect, use, disclose, or sell. Our collection, use, disclosure, and sale of Personal Information is described in our Privacy Policy above.
Right to Know/Access Information
You have the right to request access to Personal Information collected about you and information regarding the source of that information, the purposes for which we collect it, and the third parties and service providers with whom we share it. You may submit such a request as described below. To protect our customers’ Personal Information, we are required to verify your identity before we can act on your request.
Right to Request Deletion of Information
You have the right to request in certain circumstances that we delete any Personal Information that we have collected directly from you. You may submit such a request as described below. To protect our customers’ Personal Information, we are required to verify your identity before we can act on your request. We may have a reason under the law why we do not have to comply with your request, or why we may comply with it in a more limited way than you anticipated. If we do, we will explain that to you in our response.
How to Submit a Request
You may submit a request to exercise your rights to know/access or delete your Personal Information through any one of these means:
By filling out a Consumer Data Request Form available here.
By calling us at 1-800-781-9168.
Verification Procedures
In order to process your request to know/access or delete Personal Information we collect, disclose, or sell, we must verify your request. We do this by:
Asking you to
provide personal identifiers we can match against information we may have collected from you previously.
confirm your request using the email account stated in the request; and
asking you to submit proof of your California residency.
Authorized Agent
You may authorize another individual or a business registered with the California Secretary of State, called an authorized agent, to make requests on your behalf. We require that you and the individual complete notarized affidavits in order to verify the identity of the authorized agent and confirm that you have authorized them to act on your behalf. Parents of minor children may submit a birth certificate of the child in lieu of an affidavit, in order to make requests on the child’s behalf. Please see our required affidavits here.
Right to Opt Out of Sale of Personal Information to Third Parties
You have the right to opt out of any sale of your Personal Information by FULLBEAUTY Brands to third parties.
We sell information to third parties. To “sell” information means to disclose it to a company for monetary or other benefit. A company may be considered a third party either because the purpose of sharing is not an enumerated business purpose under California law, or because our contract does not restrict them from using Personal Information for other purposes.
We sell the following information:
Personal Identifiers:
We provide your contact information and device ID to directory services providers, public safety authorities, and our advertising partners.
We provide your name and postal address to credit providers if you apply for credit with us.
We provide the name and postal address of gift recipients to our advertising partners.
Payment Information: We share your payment information with credit providers if you apply for credit with us.
Protected Classifications: We may share your gender, race, ethnic origin, or religion with our advertising partners.
Commercial Information: We disclose information about the goods or services you have purchased or considered, as well as your purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies, to the FULLBEAUTY Brands and our advertising partners.
Geolocation Data: We may share location information we collect about you to our advertising partners in order to help them deliver relevant advertising.
Professional or Employment-related Information: We may disclose high-level information about your professional history to our advertising partners.
Education Information:
We may disclose high-level information about your level of education to our advertising partners.
Inferences drawn to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences or characteristics: We provide our observations about you to our advertising partners.
To exercise your right to opt out of the sale of your Personal Information to third parties, please visit our “Do Not Sell My Personal Information” webpage or call us at 1-800-781-9168.
Please note that your right to opt out does not apply to our sharing of Personal Information with service providers, who are parties we engage to perform a function on our behalf and are contractually obligated to use the Personal Information only for that function.
We may also disclose information to other entities who are not listed here when required by law or to protect our Company or other persons, as described in our Privacy Policy found at each of the FULLBEAUTY Brands websites listed below.
Brand
Website
Woman Within
https://www.womanwithin.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-ww
Brylane Home
https://www.brylanehome.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-bh
Ellos
https://www.ellos.us/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-el
Roaman's
https://www.roamans.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-rm
King Size
https://www.kingsize.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-ks
Jessica London
https://www.jessicalondon.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-jl
Swimsuits For All
https://www.swimsuitsforall.com/help/privacyPolicy.php
FullBeauty
https://www.fullbeauty.com/help-page?cid=privacy-policy-fb
Right to Information Regarding Participation in Data Sharing for Financial Incentives
You have the right to be free from discrimination based on your exercise of your CCPA rights.
From time to time we may offer incentives or discounts for consumer to sign up for our email marketing lists.
Participation in these incentives is voluntary, and you may opt out of the data sharing at any time.
Special Information For Nevada Residents
Residents of the State of Nevada have the right to opt out of the sale of certain pieces of their information to third parties who will sell or license their information to others. If you are a Nevada resident and would like to make such a request, please email PrivacyOfficer@fbbrands.com.
Changes to This Policy
We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will post any changes, and such changes will become effective when they are posted. Your continued use of our Services following the posting of any changes will mean you accept those changes.
Additional Information About Our Use of Tracking Technologies and Interest-Based Advertising
FULLBEAUTY Brands relies on partners to provide many features of our FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites and services using data about your use of the FULLBEAUTY Brands and other sites. We use cookies for the following purposes:
Website Operations: Enabling features that are necessary for providing you the services on our FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites, such as identifying you as being signed in, tracking content views, remembering your preferences and the number of times you have been shown an advertisement.
Analytics: Allowing us to understand how our services are being used, track website performance and make improvements.
Personalized Advertising: Delivering tailored advertising based on your preferences or interests across services and devices and measuring the effectiveness of ads.
Social Media: Enabling the sharing of content from our services through social networking and other websites.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if you prefer, you can usually modify your browser setting to disable or reject cookies. If you delete your cookies or if you set your browser to decline cookies, some features of the Services may not be available, work, or work as designed. You may also be able to opt out of or block tracking by interacting directly with the third-parties who conduct tracking through our Services.
You can learn more about ad serving companies and the options available to limit their collection and use of your information by visiting the websites for the Network Advertising Initiative, the Digital Advertising Alliance, and the European Interactive Digital Advertising Initiative. Similarly, you can learn about your options to opt-out of mobile app tracking by certain advertising networks through your device settings and by resetting the advertiser ID on your Apple or Android device.
Please note that opting-out of advertising networks services does not mean that you will not receive advertising while using our Services or on other websites, nor will it prevent the receipt of interest-based advertising from third parties that do not participate in these programs. It will, however, exclude you from interest-based advertising conducted through participating networks, as provided by their policies and choice mechanisms.
If you delete your cookies, you may also delete your opt-out preferences.
Your browser or device may include "Do Not Track" functionality. At this time, FULLBEAUTY Brands does not respond to browser "Do Not Track" signals.
